doity day squid.
潇洒日 乌贼
>> All right, I think it's time we go back to the office.
>> 好了，我想我们该回去了 到办公室。
>> I love everything. I love life. I love everything. I love
>> 我热爱一切。我热爱生活。我爱 一切我爱
>> Okay, stop, please. It's kind of annoying now.
>> 好了，别说了。这有点 现在可恼了。
>> But I love >> swim. Being positive is good, but
>> 但我喜欢 >> 游泳。积极是好事，但
there's a time and a place. You behaved pretty bad with Mr. Ice Cream back
有时间和地点。你的行为 冰激凌先生回来后，情况相当糟糕
there.
那里
>> I'm not trying to be mean. I'm just, you know, I'm just saying.
>> 我并不想刻薄。我只是 我只是说说
>> Oh, I see. I I I get it, Pim. I get it.
>> 哦，我明白了。我明白了，皮姆。我明白了
I wasn't being positive at all. I'm going to help this couple. I'm going to
我一点也不积极。我 要帮助这对夫妇。我要
help this wheel. I'm going to help this homeless thing.
帮助这个轮子。我要帮助这个 无家可归
>> Swim, calm down.
>>游泳，冷静。
>> Oh, I got to help those police over there with whatever they're doing.
>> 哦，我得帮助那些警察了 不管他们在做什么。
>> Swim, get back here.
>>游泳，快回来
>> Sir, get on the ground.
>>先生，请趴下。
>> Get on the ground, MAN. GET ON THE
>> 趴在地上趴下
GROUND.
地面：
>> SIR, we have you surrounded.
>> 先生，我们已经把你包围了。
>> OH MY GOSH. CHARLIE, >> DANCE. Everybody doing the swim dance.
>> 我的天啊查理： >>舞蹈。大家一起跳游泳舞
>> HE'S DOING THE SWIM DANCE. SHOOT HIM.
>> 他在跳游泳舞射他
>> Stop shooting. Shots fired. Shots fired.
>> 停止射击开枪了开枪了
>> Do a little square. Make a little love.
>> 做一点正方形。献出一点爱
Get down.
趴下
>> You really proved your loyalty to me,
>> 你真的证明了你对我的忠诚、
Charlie. Everything ended up working out in the end.
查理最终一切顺利 最后
>> Except for Squim. I feel terrible about what happened to him.
>> 除了Squim。我对 他发生了什么事。
>> What do you mean? Squim's soul just went
>> 什么意思？Squim的灵魂刚刚去了
through a 14-hour surgery. He's going to live.
经历了 14 个小时的手术。他将 住。
>> Hello there.
>> 您好。
>> I'm sorry. Who Who is Who is this? He
>> 对不起。谁是谁？他
was like the first smiling friend I ever hired. Uh used to be like really wacky
就像我第一个微笑的朋友 受雇。呃，以前真的很古怪
and stuff. Pim could back me up.
什么的。皮姆可以支持我
>> Yeah, he was. Yeah.
>> 是的是的
>> Yeah. If you saw him before, it'd make more sense.
>>是的，如果你以前见过他，就会觉得 更有意义。
>> Uh okay.
>> 好吧
[music]
[音乐]